Finding Aid for Lawrence L. Witt and Laura A. Edge papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio-Visual materials
  The Audio-Visual materials series (4.1 GB, 2000-2012) is divided into three subseries: Photographs, Oral Histories, and Miscellaneous. The Photographs subseries includes digital copies of photographs from the Collected materials series as well as a range of family photographs dating from Witt's childhood to old age. Oral Histories includes audio and video interviews with Lawrence Witt and others, mostly about their experiences in World War II. Miscellaneous includes a documentary about life on the military base in Snetterton, England from 1943-1945 as well as an audio recording of Laura Edge presenting her father's life story to the Knox Presbyterian Church in Ann Arbor.
  - Photographs
    - Family, .ZIP file
    - World War II, .ZIP file
  - Oral Histories 2000-2001, 2009, 2011, undated
    - Lawrence Witt interviewed by Andrew Edge on World War II memories
      - July 22, 2000, audio recordings; .ZIP files
      - August 24, 2000, audio recordings; .ZIP files
      - August 3, 2001, audio recordings; .ZIP files
    - Lawrence Witt's Henry Ford Motor Company stories November 16, 2009, video recording; .MP4 file
    - Lloyd Stoller interviewed by Laura Edge April 14, 2011, video recording; .ZIP file
    - James Davis on World War II memories circa 1970s, 1980s, audio recordings; .ZIP file
  - Miscellaneous 2012, undated
    - Lasting Memories, 96th Bomb Group 1943-1945, undated, video compilation; .MP4 file
    - Laura Edge's retelling of Lawrence Witt's World War II story, Knox Presbyterian Church December 14, 2012, audio recording; .WAV file